freewaytosuccess.net 2018-12-18

# Freeway to Success | Enjoy the ride

Live your dreams

Need a better view?

Love to travel?

Need a new car?

Need a vacation?

Retire in style

Your privacy is important to FREEWAY TO SUCCESS. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that FREEWAY TO SUCCESS collects, and the ways in which FREEWAY TO SUCCESS uses that personal information.

## Personal information collection

FREEWAY TO SUCCESS may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: 

  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including Name, address, phone number, email address, Social Security number, DOB)
  * information about transactions carried out over this website (including credit/debit card; account numbers) 
  * any other information that you send to FREEWAY TO SUCCESS.

## Using personal information

FREEWAY TO SUCCESS may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, FREEWAY TO SUCCESS may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your data

FREEWAY TO SUCCESS will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

FREEWAY TO SUCCESS will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. 

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that FREEWAY TO SUCCESS collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which FREEWAY TO SUCCESS operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## Updating this statement

FREEWAY TO SUCCESS may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. 

FREEWAY TO SUCCESS is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## Contact FREEWAY TO SUCCESS

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or FREEWAY TO SUCCESS treatment of your personal information, please write to:

  * by email to support@freewaytosuccess.net ; or 
  * by post to 2321 Shelburne Ave SW, Decatur, AL 35603.
